Let's do it again.
Show us!
We love you, MIRACLE.
Can you see us?
Yes, we can.
We are talking to your brain now.
We are at OHARU National Bookstore.
We are going to OHARU.
I hope we can eat delicious meat.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a happy project.
It's a good day.
We love you.
Let's go inside.
We are at OHARU.
Do you know?
YouTube doesn't allow us to eat food
easily.
Why?
I don't know.
Please.
We are going to give you a menu.
We have to guess the name of the menu.
If you get it wrong, you will be
punished.
You can't eat the menu after that.
It's a team game.
It's an individual game.
Why?
I'm crying.
It's a team game.
The person who gets it wrong and gets
the last one to eat is the winner.
I can tell the difference.
The person who gets it wrong first is
the loser.
I don't want to.
I'm going to be trusted.
OHARU chooses the menu from four
different menus.
Please choose what you like and order a
drink.
I want to call the staff.
Can I do it?
This is going to work.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's enjoy the food.
Thank you for the food.
We have a special menu list.
We can choose from here.
We don't know what we are going to do.
We can't order tuna.
The first dish has arrived.
Welcome back.
Thank you for the food.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
Please grill the meat.
Thank you, grandma.
Don't grill the meat.
The first dish has been grilled.
It's a fate.
It's the best.
Let's eat.
I don't know what it is.
It's very delicious.
Thank you for watching.
It's so good without the sauce.
I don't want to be called a loser.
Because it's so good.
But, I can't eat it.
I'll keep chewing it.
Like chewing gum.
Let's say it together.
I might cry.
It's the moment of fate.
The first meat I ate is...
Harami!
Oh, my god.
Let's say it one by one.
I'll go first.
Harami!
Harami?
Kalbi?
Harami!
Kalbi in spring.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I'm sure.
Kalbi.
Harami.
Wow!
It's beef tongue or kalbi.
What?
You!
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm sure you'll be insulted in the
comment section.
I'll be really embarrassed.
I'm so frustrated.
You're a natto.
Yes.
You're so kind.
Thank you.
Then, you can only eat sweets.
I'll do that.
I'll do the farm.
Please subscribe to my channel.
and American honey bang
itadakimasu
hey cook it
Saki is an expert, but I'm a
professional
I'm going to guess what it is.
Just by looking at it.
It looks like chicken.
You're going to be confused after you
drop it.
It's definitely chicken.
It looks like fish.
I'm going to be confused.
I don't know.
It smells.
It's a bit bland.
It looks good.
I'm going to be confused.
Let's eat!
It's cold!
I'm drooling.
I'm just enjoying myself.
Wait, wait.
This is a show.
I don't know.
Let's start.
The second menu is...
Spring Calbee!
Wait, wait.
Spring Calbee.
Spring Calbee?
Jotan.
What?
In our world.
One girl is crazy.
Jotan.
You like tongue, don't you?
But I thought this is not Calbee.
I don't know.
What is Calbee?
What do you eat tongue?
The menu is Spring Calbee.
Is it Spring Calbee?
Spring Calbee.
I did it.
The second day of the trip
Let's go!
Are you ready?
Let's start cooking!
I'm hungry.
Let's eat!
I'm so excited.
I'm getting bored.
I don't have curry and curry today.
I love meat.
I don't know about curry.
You don't know about curry.
You are saying weird things.
I know all the good things.
I can see the curry.
The thickness of the curry is
important.
I can smell the curry.
Is it good?
Yes.
Can you eat that much?
I eat a lot.
I'm so happy to meet you.
It's like a hell.
I brought a bowl of rice.
The third dish is...
Ready?
Jotan.
Are you all the same?
We haven't eaten it yet.
Please give us the answer.
The answer is Jotan.
It was so delicious.
It's soft inside but crispy outside.
I want to eat it.
If you come to Oharu, you should eat
Jotan.
You can eat Jotan forever.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The next scene is coming.
Let's do it.
I'm going to eat Jotan forever.
I've never seen it before.
I don't know.
Let's grill it.
I don't know until I taste it.
It looks delicious.
It's going to be white.
It's like a red bean paste.
It's going to be white when you grill
it.
Let's eat.
I'm sorry to say this in front of you.
I'm sorry.
It's a bad habit.
How does it taste?
Is it good?
It's like a dried persimmon.
It's good.
It's true.
What's this?
Is it alcohol?
I've never had a serious meal before.
I'm going to eat it.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'll say the name of the meat.
The fourth one is...
Chicken cartilage!
What?
Pork cartilage.
What!?
That's it?
Game over?
Can't we eat it?
So, we've finished the fourth game.
We've all been eliminated.
I'm so sorry.
We've prepared a lot of things.
We've been eliminated earlier than we
expected.
So, we've prepared a special thing.
It's the second round.
Let's have a look!
Thank you.
Please show us the first item.
What's this?
I've never seen this before.
I see.
Who is it?
I think I know what it is.
What's this?
Can you tell what it is by looking at
it?
I can tell by looking at it.
I'm curious about what it is.
Let's eat!
I think I know what it is.
Let's start the second round.
The first item is...
The second item is...
What is it?
Handmade pork hormone.
Ah!
I don't know yet.
One person might know.
The answer is...
Handmade pork hormone.
Correct!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
I'm waiting for you.
Hey, I have a bad feeling.
What?
Let's eat the grilled meat.
Hahaha.
But I'm going to faint.
I'm going to faint.
The end.
Yay!
Next!
Pork!
It's pork!
What?
I don't know what this is.
Really?
Let's eat.
Dig in.
It's a strange feeling.
I don't know what it is even if I eat
it now.
Please tell me.
You're so full.
I think you know what it is.
We usually order rice.
So, you know the general size of the
food, right?
Yes, I do.
I know the general size.
The second round.
What is the dish of Nishiname?
Ready?
Oomori!
Hikaru said Oomori.
Oomori.
I got it!
Which is it?
The answer is...
Oomori.
I got it!
It's a large portion.
There are many Yakiniku restaurants.
There are many.
What?
There are four.
Yasumori and Rina got the right answer.
Welcome!
The third round.
Next, pork.
It's all delicious.
I'm not a picky eater.
I'm going to eat the cold noodles.
I want to eat it.
The pasta is...
This is the last round.
You look energetic.
Itadakimasu.
It's spicy.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
You don't know what it is.
But, I can eat it.
You can eat it.
I'm not sure whether I can eat it or
not.
I can't help but to wonder what's wrong
with her.
I have to ask Shinji.
The third dish is...
Spicy.
Is it normal?
Medium spicy.
It's normal.
I want to eat it alone.
Please tell us what it is.
The answer is...
Spicy cold noodles.
I got it right.
That's great.
The answer is...
Yay!
Please read the question.
Cheers!
What?
That's not fair.
I don't know what this is.
You can read it.
Why are you doing this to me?
I don't know what this is.
It's easy to read.
It's not a mushroom.
It's a fried tofu.
You're right.
I made it with a lot of ingredients.
Do you want to drink?
What's this?
You'll know what it is when you eat it.
Itadakimasu!
Cheers!
Where is the green onion?
Only two of us are left.
We might win.
Are you confident?
I'm fine.
I'm confident.
Ready?
Eringi!
It's not eringi.
It's maitake mushroom.
The answer is...
maitake mushroom.
Wait.
What did you think it was?
It's eringi.
You don't like mushrooms?
It's not eringi.
Then,
Ruin won!
Yay!
I don't know what it is.
I know what it is.
I did it!
It's gourmet.
Ruin won!
Only Ruin is left.
She'll challenge it alone.
I'll read it.
It's a pickle.
I can hear her voice.
She's eating it.
It's good.
Itadakimasu!
There's a lot of ingredients.
It's rice!
What does it mean?
It's a rice ball.
It's good.
It's good?
It's kalbi-fupa.
It's spicy or yukgaejang-fupa.
I see.
I've never had fupa.
Is it your first time?
This is...
Is this kalbi?
Yes, it is.
I'm not sure if it's kalbi.
I think so.
The winner, Ritsuki Hikaru,
please give us the answer.
Kalbi-fupa.
It's spicy.
That's correct.
This is how it goes.
Everybody is making the Makai Udon
tasty,
but who are you to tell us these kind
of stories?
To be continued
This is the last one.
It's a dessert.
We'll eat all of them.
Thank you.
It's great.
We have to guess the taste of this
product.
We'll think about it.
Let's enjoy it.
Thank you.
It's refreshing.
It's delicious.
It has cookies.
We've finished eating the last dessert.
We'll answer the questions.
We have to answer the questions.
Pastel Marble.
Correct.
It was delicious.
I'm happy.
It was really delicious.
I want to eat it again.
Let's eat it again.
Please come to Haru-san and eat
delicious meat.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.